Guide to the Records of the 7th Regiment 1767-1983 (bulk 1830-1947) MS 556
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Companies, 1806-1949, 12788
  - Box and Folder:, 12940
    - Co. B: Financial Statements, 1941, 1945-1947; 13009 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Circulars/Notices, 1856-1906; 13008 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Photographs, [1900-1905]; 13007 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Co. B: Returns, Misc., 1831-1945; 13006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Co. C: Orders, 1852-1860; 13005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Co. C: Orders, 1860-1868; 13004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Co. C: Rosters, Undated; 13003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Co. C: Resolutions, 1851-1892; 13002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Co. C: Notices, Certificates, Reports, Returns, 1826-1905; 13001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - [Co. D]: Orders, 1814-1825; 13000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - [Co. D]: Orders, 1823-1825; 12999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - [Co. D]: Orders, 1823-1829; 12998 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1825-1833; 12997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1829-1841; 12996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1858-1865; 12995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1858-1878; 12994 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1866-1878; 12993 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Co. D: Resolutions, 1860-1892, 1907; 12992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Co. D: Discharges, 1869; 12991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Co. D: Notices, Rolls, Circulars, Constitution, 1821-1893; 12990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Co. D: Photographs, 1863, [1890]; 12989 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Co. E: Enlistment Records, A-L, 1942-1948; 12988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Co. E: Enlistment Records, M-Z, 1942-1948; 12987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1823, 1842-1851; 12986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1859-1863; 12985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1862-1872; 12984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Co. E: Resolutions, Roll, 1852-1892; 12983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Co. E: Reports, 1831, 1946; 12982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 July-Aug.; 12981 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Sept.; 12980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Oct.; 12979 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Nov.; 12978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Dec.; 12977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Co. F: World War I Files--General Orders, 1917 Oct.-Dec.; 12976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Jan.-Aug.; 12975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Sept.-Oct.; 12974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Nov.; 12973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Dec.; 12972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1919 Jan.; 12971 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1919 Feb.; 12970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1919 Mar.-Apr.; 12969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Co. F: World War I Files--Printed Material, 1919, undated; 12968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, Undated; 12967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Co. F: Orders, 1822-1839, 1851, 1897; 12966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Co. F: Morning Reports, 1918; 12965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Co. F: Resolutions, Rosters, Passenger Lists, 1831-1919, undated; 12964 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Co. F: Reports, 1945-1946; 12963 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Co. G: Enlistment Records, 1941-1948; 12962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Co. G: Orders, 1822, 1844-1852, 1870, 1916; 12961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Co. G: Resolutions, Minutes, 1857-1891; 12960 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Co. G: Rolls, Correspondence, 1827-1890; 12959 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Co. H: Orders, 1830-1834, 1853-1861; 12958 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Co. H: Resolutions, 1852-1892; 12957 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Co. H: Correspondence, Warrants, Reports, 1830-1854, 1906, 1949-1950; 12956 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Co. I: Manual, Training, Invites, 1866, 1878, 1909, undated; 12955 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Co. K: Minutes, 1902-1909; 12954 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Co. K: Correspondence--Samuel Hoffman, Secretary, 1904-1909; 12953 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Co. K: Correspondence--Herbert Barnes, Secretary, 12952 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Co. K: Resolutions, Correspondence, Financial, 1870-1955; 12951 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Co. K: Treasurer's Reports, 1901-1912; 12950 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Co. K: Booklets, 1940-1943; 12949 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Co. L: Reports, Memo, 1944, 1947; 12948 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Co. L: Newsletter ("The Lion"), 1937-1938, 1944; 12947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Co. L: History, [1943]; 12946 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Headquarters Co.: Enlistment Records, 1944-1949; 12945 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Band: Enlistment Records, 1941-1947; 12944 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Co. B, C, F, G, I, K: Newsletter, Undated; 12943 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Medical Detachment: Enlistment Records, 1946-1948; 12942 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Company Orders: Unidentified Companies, 1818, 1822-1824, 1862; 12941 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Rolled Rosters:, 12934
    These rolled rosters are housed in a document box in the BV section.
    - Co. A, [1850s]; 12939 (Box Unknown container 252 for instance of Co. A)
    - Co. D, Undated; 12938 (Box Unknown container 253 for instance of Co. D)
    - Co. E, 1824; 12937 (Box Unknown container 254 for instance of Co. E)
    - Co. F: Exempt Members, 1825-1828; 12936 (Box Unknown container 255 for instance of Co. F: Exempt Members)
    - Co. F, 1940; 12935 (Box Unknown container 256 for instance of Co. F)
  - Bound Volumes:, 12789
    - Co. A: By-Laws, 1842; 12933 (Volume 157)
    - Co. A: By-Laws, 1852; 12932 (Volume 158)
    - Co. A: By-Laws, 1879; 12931 (Volume 159)
    - Co. A: Membership Roll, 1806; 12930 (Volume 160)
    - Co. A: Membership Roll, 1806; 12929 (Volume 161)
    - Co. A: Rosters, 1877-1902; 12928 (Volume 162)
    - Co. A: Roll Book, 1914; 12927 (Volume 163)
    - Co. A: Minutes, 1846-1858; 12926 (Volume 164)
    - Co. A: Minutes, 1858-1875; 12925 (Volume 165)
    - Co. A: Court Martial Minutes, 1868-1884; 12924 (Volume 166)
    - Co. A: Orders (oversize), 1882-1885; 12923 (Volume 167)
    - Co. A: Daily Report, 1883; 12922 (Volume 168)
    - Co. A: Cash Book, 1848-1879; 12921 (Volume 169)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1856-1859; 12920 (Volume 170)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1860-1862; 12919 (Volume 171)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1863-1864; 12918 (Volume 172)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1868-1871; 12917 (Volume 173)
    - Co. A: Account Book--Monumental Fund, 1867-1873; 12916 (Volume 174)
    - Co. A: Receipt Book, 1861-1893; 12915 (Volume 175)
    - Co. A: Rifle Practice, 1882-1883; 12914 (Volume 176)
    - Co. A: Rifle Practice, 1884-1885; 12913 (Volume 177)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (in envelope), 1830, 1834, 1841, 1844, 1848; 12912 (Volume 178)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (boxed), 1871, 1878, 1882; 12911 (Volume 179)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1850; 12910 (Volume 180)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1853; 12909 (Volume 181)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1856; 12908 (Volume 182)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1858; 12907 (Volume 183)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1862; 12906 (Volume 184)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1871; 12905 (Volume 185)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (2 copies), 1878; 12904 (Volume 186)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (2 copies), 1893; 12903 (Volume 187)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (3 copies), 1897; 12902 (Volume 188)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (3 copies), 1911; 12901 (Volume 189)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1913; 12900 (Volume 190)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1917; 12899 (Volume 191)
    - Co. B: Rosters, 1858-1917; 12898 (Volume 192)
    - Co. B: Member Roll, 1806-1825; 12897 (Volume 193)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, 1843-1867; 12896 (Volume 194)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, 1868-1889; 12895 (Volume 195)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, 1889-1910; 12894 (Volume 196)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, Honorary Members, 1859-1865; 12893 (Volume 197)
    - Co. B: Register of Members, Ex-Members, Veterans, 1864-1910; 12892 (Volume 198)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1826-1839; 12891 (Volume 199)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1847-1852; 12890 (Volume 200)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1852-1857; 12889 (Volume 201)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1857-1862; 12888 (Volume 202)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1914-1918; 12887 (Volume 203)
    - Co. B: Record of Services, 1861-1863; 12886 (Volume 204)
    - Co. B: Account Book, 1827-1838; 12885 (Volume 205)
    - Co. B: Nonsense Rhymes, 1880; 12884 (Volume 206)
    - Co. B: Aqueduct Guard, 1917; 12883 (Volume 207)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1846; 12882 (Volume 208)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1860; 12881 (Volume 209)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1876; 12880 (Volume 210)
    - Co. C: By-Laws (2), 1884; 12879 (Volume 211)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1888; 12878 (Volume 212)
    - Co. C: Rosters, 1887; 12877 (Volume 213)
    - Co. C: Minute Book, 1847-1854; 12876 (Volume 214)
    - Co. C: Roster (rolled, in metal tube), 1806; 12875 (Volume 215)
    - Co. D: By-Laws, 1823-1893; 12874 (Volume 216)
    - Co. D: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1819-1846; 12873 (Volume 217)
    - Co. D: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1845-1871; 12872 (Volume 218)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1831-1840; 12871 (Volume 219)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1841-1852; 12870 (Volume 220)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1852-1859; 12869 (Volume 221)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1860-1866; 12868 (Volume 222)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1866-1875; 12867 (Volume 223)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1875-1882; 12866 (Volume 224)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1882-1887; 12865 (Volume 225)
    - Co. D: Minute Book, 1823-1831; 12864 (Volume 226)
    - Co. D: Orderly Book, 1828-1839; 12863 (Volume 227)
    - Co. D: Orderly Book, 1840-1859; 12862 (Volume 228)
    - Co. D: Orders (oversize), 1873-1885; 12861 (Volume 229)
    - Co. D: Account Book, 1817-1845; 12860 (Volume 230)
    - Co. E: By-Laws, 1866; 12859 (Volume 231)
    - Co. E: By-Laws, 1887; 12858 (Volume 232)
    - Co. E: Roll Book, 1893; 12857 (Volume 233)
    - Co. E: Roll Book, 1899; 12856 (Volume 234)
    - Co. E: Secretary's Book, 1830-1847; 12855 (Volume 235)
    - Co. E: Report Book, 1834-1844; 12854 (Volume 236)
    - Co. E: Minute Book, 1848-1861; 12853 (Volume 237)
    - Co. E: Minute Book, 1861-1876; 12852 (Volume 238)
    - Co. E: Minute Book, 1876-1889; 12851 (Volume 239)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1851-1859; 12850 (Volume 240)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1872-1883; 12849 (Volume 241)
    - Co. E: Account Book, 1834-1851; 12848 (Volume 242)
    - Co. E: Returns (oversize), 1842-1859; 12847 (Volume 243)
    - Co. E: Account Book--Returns of Delinquents, 1878-1891; 12846 (Volume 244)
    - Co. F: By-Laws, 1834-1902; 12845 (Volume 245)
    - Co. F: Rolls, Roster, Committees, 1874-1891; 12844 (Volume 246)
    - Co. F: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1819-1900; 12843 (Volume 247)
    - Co. F: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1819-1940; 12842 (Volume 248)
    - Co. F: Roll Book, Undated; 12841 (Volume 249)
    - Co. F: Daily Report, 1883; 12840 (Volume 250)
    - Co. F: Orderly Book, 1834-1847; 12839 (Volume 251)
    - Co. F: Orders, 1836-1845; 12838 (Volume 252)
    - Co. F: Orders, 1854-1863; 12837 (Volume 253)
    - Co. F: Court Martial Returns (oversize), 1875-1893; 12836 (Volume 254)
    - Co. F: Scrapbook, 1855-1866; 12835 (Volume 255)
    - Co. F: Record Book--Rifle Practice, 1880-1885; 12834 (Volume 256)
    - Co. G: By-Laws, 1833; 12833 (Volume 257)
    - Co. G: By-Laws, 1861-1875; 12832 (Volume 258)
    - Co. G: Rosters, 1888; 12831 (Volume 259)
    - Co. G: Information Booklet, 1882; 12830 (Volume 260)
    - Co. G: Monthly Report, 1868-1872; 12829 (Volume 261)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1834-1852; 12828 (Volume 262)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1852-1861; 12827 (Volume 263)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1861-1876; 12826 (Volume 264)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1876-1891; 12825 (Volume 265)
    - Co. G: Orderly Book, 1865-1871; 12824 (Volume 266)
    - Co. G: Orders, 1871-1881; 12823 (Volume 267)
    - Co. G: Enlistment Roll (oversize), 1859-1914; 12822 (Volume 268)
    - Co. H: By-Laws, 1829-1885; 12821 (Volume 269)
    - Co. H: By-Laws, 1861; 12820 (Volume 270)
    - Co. H: Roll Books, 1846-1890; 12819 (Volume 271)
    - Co. H: Roll Book, 1876; 12818 (Volume 272)
    - Co. H: Record Book, 1827-1829; 12817 (Volume 273)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1827-1834; 12816 (Volume 274)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1834-1835; 12815 (Volume 275)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1835-1844; 12814 (Volume 276)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1844-1855; 12813 (Volume 277)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1855-1863; 12812 (Volume 278)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1864-1875; 12811 (Volume 279)
    - Co. I: By-Laws (in box), 1858, 1870, 1877, 1885; 12810 (Volume 280)
    - Co. I: By-Laws (2 copies), 1870; 12809 (Volume 281)
    - Co. I: By-Laws, 1877; 12808 (Volume 282)
    - Co. I: Rosters, 1887-1922; 12807 (Volume 283)
    - Co. I: Roster, 1838-1913; 12806 (Volume 284)
    - Co. I: Roster, 1838-1938; 12805 (Volume 285)
    - Co. I: Minutes, 1879-1891; 12804 (Volume 286)
    - Co. I: Minutes, 1892-1908; 12803 (Volume 287)
    - Co. I: Minutes, 1908-1917; 12802 (Volume 288)
    - Co. I: Account Book, 1869-1872; 12801 (Volume 289)
    - Co. I: Accounts Receivable, 1879-1880; 12800 (Volume 290)
    - Co. I: Court Martial--Fines Levied, 1863-1865; 12799 (Volume 291)
    - Co. I: Court Martial--Fines Levied, 1870-1872; 12798 (Volume 292)
    - Co. I: Manual, 1935; 12797 (Volume 293)
    - Co. I: 'Tin Soldiers', 1914; 12796 (Volume 294)
    - Co. K: By-Laws, 1909; 12795 (Volume 295)
    - Co. K: Rosters, 1877-1930; 12794 (Volume 296)
    - Co. K: Minute Book, 1895-1906; 12793 (Volume 297)
    - Co. K: Minute Book, 1906-1913; 12792 (Volume 298)
    - Co. K: Memoranda, Undated; 12791 (Volume 299)
    - Co. M: Roster and By-Laws, 1911; 12790 (Volume 300)
- Series III: Depot (Home) Battalion/Aqueduct Service, 1916-1929, 12782
  This series contains materials related to the Depot (Home) Battalion, 7th Infantry who defended the aqueduct in Pleasantville, New York during World War I in 1917. The materials summarize the duties of the men defending the aqueduct or relate to the Aqueduct Association, its veterans organization.
  - Roster, Depot Battalion, 7th Infantry, 1916; 12787 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Greyjackets on the Aqueduct, 1917", 1922; 12786 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Aqueduct Association--Correspondence, 1927-1929; 12785 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Aqueduct Association--Materials re: Fifth and Sixth Annual Outings, 1924-1925; 12784 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, 1917 Sept.; 12783 (Volume 301)
- Series IV: Francis D. Landon, 1908-1918, 12600
  Francis G. Landon (1859-1947) was a politician from New York City. He joined the 7th Regiment as a private, rose through the ranks and was promoted to Major. During the period ca.1912 to ca.1916, he was involved in the education of military officers, initially as a student, but later, apparently, as an instructor. Following the United States' declaration of war against Germany in 1917, Landon served as Morale Officer at Camp Merritt, NJ. This series consists of material that Landon accumulated primarily during these two stages of his career. The series is divided into three principal subseries. These are: General Correspondence, Military Education, and Camp Merritt, NJ.
  - Subseries 1: General Correspondence, 1909-1915, 12777
    The General Correspondence subseries consists of personal letters to Landon and his retained copies of his replies. Letters received by Landon are arranged chronologically in a folder titled General Correspondence - Letters Received. Landon's replies are arranged alphabetically, with one folder for each recipient of Landon's letters. The letters concern two subjects: the study of military history and a proposed program of rifle practice in colleges.
    - Letters Received, 1909, 1914-1915, undated; 12781 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Major [ ] Hutchinson - Letters Received, 1915; 12780 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - [ ] Parker - Letters Received, 1909; 12779 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Gen. [Chas. F.] Roe - Letters Received, 1909; 12778 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Military Education, 1912-1917, 12728
    Material in the Military Education subseries consists primarily of small booklets of problem-solving exercises for military officers. These booklets were published by the Army Service Schools, where Landon attended classes during the academic year 1913 - 1914, and perhaps at other times. For purposes of the arrangement of this series, these booklets are referred to as Map Problems, the genre name applied to most of the booklets. In those instances that Landon kept a map with the booklet, they are housed together. Otherwise, maps are housed separately. Also included in this subseries are Landon's solutions to some of the Map Problems, evidently composed as course work, and some problems that appear to have been composed by Landon, perhaps for courses that he taught. This material is arranged according to the particular school that issued it, or, if no specific school is identified, the course to which it pertains. If no school or course is specified, the folder title indicates only the type of material found within it.
    Landon appears to have taught at least one course in military tactics. Some material in the collection appears to be lecture notes or typewritten handouts that accompanied lectures. It some cases, it is unclear whether these notes and handouts are from lectures that Landon attended, or whether he composed them for lectures that he delivered. Some notes and typescripts pertaining to Landon's military education at Fort Leavenworth are identified as such.
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1912-1913; 12776 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1913-1914; 12775 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1914-1915; 12774 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1915-1916; 12773 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Army School of the Line - [Map Problems] - Terrain Exercise #6, 1913; 12772 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Army School of the Line - [Map Problems] - The Rifle in War, 1913-1914; 12771 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Army School of the Line - Organization of the German Army, 1913-1914; 12770 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Map Problems, 1912; 12769 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Map Problems, 1913; 12768 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Map Problems, 1914; 12767 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - List of Lessons & Exercises, 1914; 12766 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Topics for Discussion, 1914; 12765 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Special Class for Field Officers - Tactical Ride, 1914; 12764 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Special Class for Field Officers - Map Maneuvers, 1912-1914; 12763 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Army Field Engineers' School - Course List, 1913-1914; 12762 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Army Field Engineers' School - Quiz, 1914 Jan.; 12761 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Provisional Officers' Class - Map Problems, 1917; 12760 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - [Provisional Officers' Class] - Musketry Problems, 1917, undated; 12759 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Army Staff College - Course in Historical Research, [1912-1913]; 12758 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Army Service Schools - Map Problems - Solutions Submitted by Landon (1 of 2), 1914; 12757 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Army Service Schools - Map Problems - Solutions Submitted by Landon (2 of 2), 1914; 12756 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Army Service Schools - Map Problems - Tables of Troop Blocks for Maps, 1914; 12755 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Army Service Schools - Memoranda, 1914; 12754 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Army Service Schools - Reprint of Order - 9th U.S. Inf., 1914; 12753 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Army Service Schools - Printed Examination Booklets, 1917, undated; 12752 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - [Army Service Schools] - Proposed Solution to Griepenkerl Problem, Undated; 12751 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - [Army Service Schools] - Residence List of Officers at Fort Leavenworth, 1914; 12750 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - [Army Service Schools] - Invitation, [1914]; 12749 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - School of the Line and Staff - Map Problems, 1914-1916; 12748 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Board of Instruction - 7th Reg't - Instructions to First Year Class, 1915; 12747 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - [Map Problems] - Suggestions for the Preparation of Maneuver Problems, 1913; 12746 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - [Map Problems] - [Problems Composed by Landon], 1914; 12745 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Notes on Map Drawing/Map Reading, [1915]; 12744 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - [Lecture Notes] - Fort Leavenworth, 1914; 12743 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Notes on Civil War Battles, Undated; 12742 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Typewritten Notes on Military Tactics, 1915, 1916, undated; 12741 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Synopses of Books, Undated; 12740 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Sample Quiz Questions and Answers, [1914]; 12739 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Quizzes, 1914-1916; 12738 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Examination - American Campaigns, [1914]; 12737 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - NY Service Schools - Map Problem #3, 1915-1916; 12736 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - NY School of the Line and Staff - Bulletins, 1914-1915; 12735 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - NY School of the Line and Staff - Infantry Officers' Examinations, 1915-1916; 12734 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - NY School of the Line Map Problem #6, 1915-1916; 12733 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - NY School of the Line - Organizational Table of a U.S. Infantry Division, 1915-1916; 12732 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - NY National Guard - Typescript of Pamphlet re Trench Warfare, 1916; 12731 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Advertisement for Book - Battle Fire Training, Undated; 12730 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Typescript - Manual for Infantrymen, Undated; 12729 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Camp Merritt, 1918-1919, 12664
    The Camp Merritt, NJ subseries contains, for the most part, material created by or relating to the Morale Office at that facility. A small portion of the material in the subseries concerns the Camp in general, and is not specific to the Morale Office. Included is correspondence to and from the Morale Office. Note that this folder group is distinct from the General Correspondence subseries, and includes material addressed to other offices on Camp Merritt, but routed to and answered by the Morale Office. Letters received by the Morale Office are arranged chronologically in a folder titled Morale Office - Letters Received. Retained copies of the Morale Office's replies are arranged in folders by the name of the letter's recipient. Subjects include: programs to maintain the morale of soldiers stationed at Camp Merritt (e.g. sporting events, Christmas decorations, 4th of July fireworks, etc.); commemorative medals for the schoolchildren of Bergen County, NJ, to be paid for by the personnel of the Camp; and weekly reports to the war Department on the state of the soldiers' morale.
    - Morale Office - Letters Received, 1918-1919; 12727 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Morale Office - Letters Received - Letters from Children, 1919; 12726 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Morale Office - Circular Letters Received, 1918, undated; 12725 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Morale Office - Major [ ] Axton -, 1918-1919; 12724 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Morale Office - Bank of Coney Island, 1919; 12723 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Morale Office - Chaplain [ ] Beebe, 1919; 12722 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Morale Office - Dept. of Labor, 1919; 12721 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Morale Office - Dreges & Clost, 1918; 12720 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Morale Office - Wm. H. Edwards, 1919; 12719 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Morale Office - [ ] Evans, 1919; 12718 (Box 27, Folder 18)